trovix.com 2007-09-23

# Trovix, Inc. - Privacy Policy

Trovix respects the privacy of our customers. As part of this commitment the following privacy statement highlights our policies as they pertain to protecting our customers' information. If you object to any or all of this Privacy Statement you should not use the site.

**Definitions**

"Trovix Sites" - the Trovix service at recruit.trovix.com and corporate web site [www.trovix.com](http://www.trovix.com/). "Company" - A company who has subscribed to the Trovix service. "Customer" - A user of the Trovix service who is acting on behalf of a Company. "Agreement" - The legal document signed which is the basis for the Company subscription to Trovix (Beta Agreement or Service Level Agreement)

**Information Collection**

As part of the use of the Trovix Sites, Customers can upload job requisitions, resumes, and other data to the Trovix Sites. In addition Trovix collects certain information about the Company and Customers who use the service. Job requisitions, resumes, and other information uploaded to the Trovix Sites by Customers is owned by the Company. Personal information that is collected as part of the registration process is owned by Trovix.

**Information Usage**

The personal information collected by Trovix is used to set up the Trovix service for the Company and its Customers. In addition it may be used to ensure the delivery of excellent service, aid in the resolution of technical issues, and allow Trovix to update Customers with regards to new features and services.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

Trovix will maintain the confidentiality of our Customer's information submitted to the site. This information will only be disclosed to third parties (such as partners or vendors) as follows: 1. If required by law 2. As stated in the Agreement. 3. As stated on Trovix Sites when the information was collected. (For example as stated in the user agreement and privacy statement at the time registration information is collected.) 4. As aggregate information not associated with an individual Customer, Company, or resume 5. In the event a payment processor is used to process payments (in this case the processor will not store the data). 6. In the event Trovix is acquired, merged or other change of control or liquidated.

**Data Collection**

**Registration:** Trovix collects information such as name, company name, address, phone number and email address from the Trovix Customers. The purpose of collecting this information is to grant access to the Trovix Sites as well as allowing Trovix to contact Customers as described in Information Usage. This information can be viewed and modified at any time on the site.

**Job Description:** Customers submit information describing employment openings to the Trovix Sites on behalf of the Company. Customers can only view Job Descriptions belonging to their respective Companies. The information provided remains the property of the Company.

**Resumes:** Resumes are entered into the Trovix system from time to time. This data may be sent via email or uploaded directly to the Trovix Sites. Customers are only permitted to view resumes that belong to their respective Companies. Resumes remain the property of the Company whose Customer sent them to the Trovix Sites.

**Resume Searches:** Trovix allows for advanced searches to be conducted on resumes. Searches can use key words, job descriptions or both. Job descriptions are stored in the system when they are created. Key word searches are stored in the system in aggregate with no identifying information. Trovix uses this information, in aggregate only, to constantly enhance the quality of search results by enhancing the Trovix knowledge base. This information is the property of Trovix.

**Resume Rating:** Customers are able to provide feedback on the results of searches in order for the system to learn Customer individual preferences. The Customer preference information is stored in the system for the sole purpose of enhancing the quality of the search. Customers can modify this information on the Trovix Sites. Trovix maintains a log of this information for the proper operation of the service. This information is owned by the Customer's respective Company.

**Attribute Profiles:** The resume rating process creates a profile of a Customer's preferences used to enhance the quality of the search results. This data is stored in the system and is used solely for improving the quality of the search results. This information is owned by the Customer's respective Company.

**Incoming email:** Users may send Trovix email during their use of the Trovix Sites. These email messages are processed and then may either be destroyed or kept for future reference. This information is owned by Trovix.

**Log Analysis**

The Trovix Sites run on Web Servers which collect information such as IP addresses, URLs and other information specific to the browser used to access the Trovix Sites. This information is used to administer the Trovix Sites, trouble shoot technical issues and analyze aggregate traffic trends. This information is not associated with an individual Customer.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small amounts of data that web sites can send to a user's browser. This data is then sent to the site with every user request. There are two types of Cookies, session based or persistent.

Session based Cookies are set by the site and expire when the user leaves the site. Trovix uses these Cookies to track the login status of users. These cookies are encrypted and contain no personal user information. Customers who disable Cookies in their browser will be able to browse the Trovix Sites but will not be able to log in and use the service.

Persistent Cookies are those that can be set by a Web Site and remain on the Customer machine even after leaving the Trovix Sites. Trovix Sites do not use Persistent Cookies.

**Third Party Sites**

Trovix Sites may include links to other sites. These sites have their own privacy policies which users are encouraged to read. Trovix is not responsible for the privacy policies of these sites nor the use of information submitted on those sites.

**Security**

Trovix knows that information Customers submit to the Trovix Sites is confidential in nature. As such, Trovix uses industry standard security measures to safeguard Company and Customer information against loss, misuse and alteration while under the Trovix's control. These measures include 128 bit SSL encryption of all web traffic between the Trovix web servers and the user browser and requiring unique user names and passwords to access the Trovix Sites. Trovix Sites use security systems including firewalls and are hosted in a secure location with restricted access to the physical computers that run the Trovix Sites. Questions about security should be forwarded to Trovix through the "Feedback" link.

**Opt Out Policy**

Customers can indicate their desire to stop receiving email messages from Trovix by contacting Trovix through the "Feedback" link and indicating their e-mail and user name. Trovix may also, at times, send emails to users offering them to opt in to different communications from Trovix.

**Correct or Update Information**

Customers can correct or update any personal information submitted to the Trovix Sites at any time by contacting Trovix through the "Feedback" link.

**Notification of Changes**

Should Trovix change its privacy policy it will communicate these changes by posting the new statement on the Trovix Sites. Customers will have 30 days from the date of posting to notify Trovix if they do not accept the changes. In this case the Customer information will be treated in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information was collected.
